[
    {
        "question": "Lombard Street in London is the equivalent to which famous street in the US?",
        "answer": "Wall Street"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Hagia Sophia is located in what country?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what European country is the Po River?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wellington is the capital of what island nation?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pearl Harbor is located on which Hawaiian island?",
        "answer": "Oahu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country comprises most of the Jutland peninsula?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which countries share the island of Borneo with Indonesia?",
        "answer": "Malaysia and Brunei"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the closest foreign country to the US which does not touch the US?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official language of Egypt?",
        "answer": "Arabic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What agricultural crop is Cuba`s main export?",
        "answer": "Sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the most densely populated country in the world?",
        "answer": "Monaco"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Japanese name for Japan?",
        "answer": "Nippon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What continent includes Iran?",
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What leaf appears on the Canadian flag?",
        "answer": "The Maple Leaf"
    },
    {
        "question": "What line on a map connects places of equal rainfall?",
        "answer": "Isohyet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Capital of Guadeloupe?",
        "answer": "Basse-Terre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Egypt to the south?",
        "answer": "Sudan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nashville is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Tennessee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the island that separates the two waterfalls at Niagara Falls?",
        "answer": "Goat Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the opposite of the Orient?",
        "answer": "The Occident"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Sooner State`?",
        "answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of Pittsburgh is located in which state?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Keystone State`?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the two letter postal abbreviation for the state of Virginia?",
        "answer": "VA"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1620, the Pilgrims established the Plymouth colony in which present-day US state?",
        "answer": "Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Cape Lookout National Seashore?",
        "answer": "North Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which English town can you attend the annual Jane Austen Festival?",
        "answer": "Bath"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the Dragon Blood Tree",
        "answer": "Yemen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which East Asian country celebrates Golden Week?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is it illegal to ride a horse over 10 mph?",
        "answer": "Indiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which state is the Edmund Pettus Bridge located?",
        "answer": "Alabama"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s longest underwater cave?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "The `nene` is the official bird of which state?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most populous city in the Middle East?",
        "answer": "Cairo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find an underwater volcano called `Kick `em Jenny`?",
        "answer": "Caribbean Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. president is honored by a statue in Ballybunion, Ireland?",
        "answer": "Bill Clinton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has an extreme version of swinging called kiiking?",
        "answer": "Estonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Queen Elizabeth need permission from to enter the City of sLondon?",
        "answer": "The Lord Mayor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the 3 major islands of the Philippines?",
        "answer": "Luzon, Visayas and Mindanao"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the longest river in the Philippines?",
        "answer": "Cagayan River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest major city in the Philippines?",
        "answer": "Cebu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which place is dubbed as `The Salad Bowl of the Philippines`?",
        "answer": "Benguet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the highest point in the Philippines?",
        "answer": "Mt. Apo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s largest known beaver dam?",
        "answer": "Alberta, Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Antananarivo is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Madagascar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Antananarivo is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Madagascar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean is the island of Madagascar located in?",
        "answer": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean is the island-nation of Madagascar located in?",
        "answer": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Fiji?",
        "answer": "Suva"
    },
    {
        "question": "Suva is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Fiji"
    }
]